Hi, I'm Jennifer Cail.
Our next step is going to be creaming the butter.
For the amount of butter that we are going to be using, is 1 1/2 sticks which is also 3/4 of a cup of butter.
I highly recommend using a stand mixer.
It will definitely save your arms verses to try to beat it with a wooden spoon.
Make sure you get all of the paper off.
You don't want to leave any paper inside for it to be baked in the cookies.
I'm going to use a flat beater.
If you use a wire whisk, it's not going to be able to handle the butter unless the butter is super super soft, almost melted.
But then you won't be able to work with the dough with a wire whisk, so you want a flat beater.
You also want to make sure that your butter is room temperature.
Try to let it sit out for at least half an hour if not an hour or so before you are ready to use it.
That will ensure that it's going to be soft enough to easily be beaten.
You want to start it out at a slower speed just to get the butter moving a little bit you don't want to try and work your stand mixer to hard.
We are going to speed it up a little bit to really cream that butter.
Now you can see that our butter has been nicely creamed and we are ready for the next step.